<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on</title><link>https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/tags/introduction/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:48:47 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/tags/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Andres</title><link>https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/blog/andres/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:48:47 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/blog/andres/</guid><description>Howdy! My name is Andres Mena and I am a senior Technology Management student at Texas A&amp;amp;M and a member of the Corps of Cadets. I am from Del Rio, TX which is a small town on the border with Mexico, southwest of San Antonio.
After I graduate I plan on commissioning as a lieutenant into the Marine Corps, hopefully as an intelligence officer. This summer I plan on doing an internship with an IT company so I can get some more hands on experience.</description></item><item><title>Blake</title><link>https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/blog/blake/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:48:47 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/blog/blake/</guid><description>Howdy!
My name is Blake Taber, and I am currently a junior TCMG student here at Texas A&amp;amp;M. I am from a town called Wylie, which is just on the northeast side of Dallas. After graduation, I&amp;rsquo;m wanting to move out of the country, ideally to somewhere in western Europe, but would be open to other experiences as well. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a particular dream job, but would be interested in database administration.</description></item><item><title>Bradly</title><link>https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/blog/bradly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:48:47 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/blog/bradly/</guid><description>Howdy
My name is Bradly Felix and i am junior Technology Management major from Jacksonville, Florida. I have a couple of experiences/internships ranging from working at Convergys and Visa as a IT desktop support intern. Upon graduation i hope to be working somewhere in the homesecurity side of IT.
As for my life outside of school, i am currently a member of Aggie Transition Camp and Phi Beta Lambda. My hobbies include working out (bench 225 club), reading, playing video games, and helping out in the community.</description></item><item><title>Corey</title><link>https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/blog/corey/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:48:47 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/blog/corey/</guid><description>Howdy! My name is Corey Whitfield and I am a senior here at Texas A&amp;amp;M University. I came to this university to enroll in the Technology Management program so I can pursue a career as a Database Administrator. The reason why I want to be a Database Administrator is because I enjoy the complexity of dealing with SQL queries. I took a Database course last semester and I have to admit that I had fun trying to figure out the most simplistic but yet complicated problem.</description></item><item><title>Kyle</title><link>https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/blog/kyle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:48:47 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/blog/kyle/</guid><description>Howdy!</description></item><item><title>Viet</title><link>https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/blog/viet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:48:47 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://CoreSSJ.github.io/project2/blog/viet/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>